Guide to the Woolmer Collection of Cormac McCarthy
The Wittliff Collections
- Correspondence, 1969-2006
  - McCarthy to Woolmer. Als, 2 pages, February 25, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    "Thank you very much for the book [Bibliography of Malcolm Lowry]. I think is quite elegant and I've enjoyed looking through it. I think Under the Volcano is an amazing book and Lowry a genuinely tragic figure…" Discusses Malcolm Lowry and Albert Erskine's relationship with him. "Thank you also for the excerpt from Rubin's book on Southern literature…I see these excerpts come from pages as advanced as #581. How long does this tome continue? I didnt know there was that much Southern Literature…" Mentions he is back from New Orleans where friend has been filming a movie with Richard Gere.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Carbon, 1 page, March 19, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Sorry he missed McCarthy's phone call; Asks about status of Curtis book.
  - McCarthy to Woolmer. ALS, 1 page, June 3, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    "Sorry I missed you on the telephone. Perel was stirring about the Curtis again, but it has subsided again since…Random House sends the proof cover of their paperback issue of Suttree – due out in October. A 'Vintage Contemporary' the jacket says. Do you love it? Gallimard has bought the rights to Blood Meridian." He's written a play.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Carbon, 1 page, July 15, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Sending a "have-list" of his CMcC collection [not included]; offers to buy anything McCarthy has that's not on the list.
  - McCarthy to Woolmer. ALS, 1 page, July 15, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    "Aint you a good chap to send the play? I thought it quite good…" Mentions that his agent has banned him for showing anyone a copy of his new play "Something to do with his strategy…"
  - McCarthy to Woolmer. ALS, 3 pages (2 sheets), August 27, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    "Thanks for the correspondence – The Writer's Choice is something I would not have seen otherwise. Tobias Wolff is a very agreeable chap…I was pleased to see I remain in his good graces…" Lists McCarthy editions that Woolmer might not have in his. "My translator was here a few weeks ago. Charming gentleman who loved the desert and kept crying out 'formidéble!' at everything…I'm working on a whale story. May go to Argentina in the fall with a biologist friend who studies them…" Asks whom else Woolmer collects. Mentions Michael Ondaatje and Guy Davenport.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, October 29, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Trying to get French translations. Discusses book collecting (Yount, Gilbert White Graham Swift) and bibliography writing.
  - Woolmer to Robert Penn Warren. TLS, with Warren's holograph answer, November 3, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Inquiring about McCarthy excerpt in text book. Warren's response indicates that he did not publish an excerpt in Understanding Fiction, but there might be a reference to McCarthy.
  - McCarthy to Woolmer. Postcard, November 5, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    "This, as the card says, comes to you from Ushuzia [Argentina], the southernmost city in the world…".
  - McCarthy to Woolmer. ALS, 1 page (no envelope), circa 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    "Just back from the Argentine – a good trip. Spent about 3 weeks among the whales at peninsula Valdez…[Guy] Davenport is supposed to have a new collection of essays out from North Point. I thought the first collection was just a first rate piece of work…Just finished a very interesting book called The Body in Pain by Elaine Scanny…" Sending a Yount book found for 50 cents.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, December 24, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Thanking him for Yount book. Recommends Robert Herring books. Enclosing Anatole Broyard New York Times Book Review article, "To Squalor, With Love" that references Suttree. [clipping included].
  - McCarthy to Woolmer. ALS, 1 page, February 28, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    "Good to hear from you. I see I'm going to have to start proofreading my letters before I send them off…" Spent Christmas with his brother in Knoxville then went to California for a week. "I'm now holed up and back to work. My whale biologist friend Roger is in the Seychelles. I think I'm in the wrong business…"
  - McCarthy to Woolmer. ALS, 2 pages, January 5, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    "Thank you for the clipping from the NY Times. I'm just back from California, where a theatre group did a reading of a play I wrote…I've finished a rough draft of a novel [All the Pretty Horses] – Mexico & Texas in the 1940's – and started another one with much the same setting…"
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, January 9, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Asking if McCarthy has an extra copy of the play script.
  - McCarthy to Woolmer. ALS, 2 pages (one sheet), March 21, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    "I aint forgot you…" Is hesitant to send copy of script "because I intend some time to do some more work on it. There are elements that are just not clean…" Recommends [Bruce Chatwin's] Songlines.
  - Woolmer to Ken Lopez. Carbon, 1 page, April 4, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Inquiring about advance copies of Outer Dark and Child of God.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, May 19, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Passing along compliment from Bruce Chatwin. Also inquiring about selling his papers; is establishing a relationship with a university library that would be in position to purchase his archives. Advises to never throw anything away.
  - McCarthy to Woolmer. ALS, 2 pages, November 17, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    "I've been in my non communication mode for some time but I have to write and thank you for the very handsome book…I appreciate your inquiry about my manuscripts. I've got – I suppose – most of them packed away in a storage locker along with corrected proofs and galleys and such. I dont really propose to do any thing with this junk except keep it…Anyway I'm still at work on my little projects I've finished rough rafts of 2 novels and started a third. They are all three connected…"
  - McCarthy to Woolmer. ALS, 3 pages, April 8, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    "Sorry for the long hiatus in our correspondence…" Just received a batch of reviews [All the Pretty Horses]. "I was very distressed over Chatwin's death. A talented and honest man and a decent human being – the perfect candidate, in other words for the fates to single out…I've lost another writer friend two weeks ago – Ed Abbey. I think he came across in his writing as some thing of a curmudgen [sic] but he was a kind and generous man – qualities, sad to say, not common to writers…" Refers to Woolmer's comments about selling his manuscripts, "I get requests from institutions wanting me to send them my manuscripts. I sometimes wonder vaguely what they think I use for money. I've been a full time professional writer for 28 years and I've never received a royalty check. That, I'll betcha, is a record…"
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1989, April 27, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Shocked over Chatwin's death; discusses Henry Miller and Saul Bellow manuscripts sales; advises not to give away his papers.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Carbon, 1 page, August 22, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Inquiring how to pronounce "Suttree." Arguing with friend that it is "Suhtree."
  - McCarthy to Woolmer. ALS, 2 pages (1 sheet), September 6, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    "Thanks for your note. You win the wager. It never occurred to me that folks would pronounce Suttree to rhyme with shoe tree but they do…"
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, March 14, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Suggests bringing Dr. Thomas F. Staley, Director of the Harry Ransom Center at the University of Texas to El Paso to meet McCarthy.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Carbon, 1 page, June 10, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Woolmer and Staley thinking of coming out in to El Paso in October.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, August 15, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Sending Paul Watkins novel; more about October trip possibility.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, August 31, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Staley suggests October 15, 16, or 17.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Carbon, 1 page, May 18, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Attended American Academy awards and disappointed McCarthy was a no-show. Hopes to see him in El Paso in fall.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, January 15, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Thanking for proof copy of All the Pretty Horses; praises book. Will be in Austin for dinner for Elizabeth Hardwick, but won't make it to El Paso.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, April 21, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Asking about McCarthy signing copies of books; offers to broker deal for his papers with the HRHRC.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, June 4, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Thanking for signed books. Inquires about scripts for The Stonemason and The Gardner's Son.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, September 11, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Inquiring about The Stonemason.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, October 3, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Recently spent the day with Guy Davenport; went to The University of Tennessee library and found "Wake for Susan" and "A Drowning Incident" published in the Phoenix.
  - McCarthy to Woolmer. Printed invitation, 1 page, December 7, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    "Cormac McCarthy invites you – on the occasion of his receiving the National Book Award for 1992 – to a party to be held on Saturday December 19th at the law offices of Malcolm McGregor and Bobby Perel."
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Carbon, 1 page with typed annotations, December 10, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Sending Thomas Staley's review of All the Pretty Horses for Harper & Queen. TMs included, inscribed: "To Howard Woolmer, I've cut and cut for Harper and Queen. I could write a book on this fine novel. Best wishes, Tom 12/7/92"
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, January 1, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Thanking for party and lunch; Suggests limited edition of The Stonemason.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, March 10, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Thanking for Stonemason; sending check for $100; congratulations on National Book Critics Circle Award.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, April 10, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Sending article in Firsts.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, May 1, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Reporting on purchase of French editions during Paris trip.
  - Woolmer to Editions Robert Laffont. Photocopy, 1 page, May 4, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Inquiring about French editions.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy, May 25, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Update on All the Pretty Horses printings.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Carbon, 1 page, July 13, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Complimenting "The Wolf Trapper."
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, annotated, November 21, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    More about collecting foreign editions; asking to publish limited edition of The Stonemason.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Carbon, 1 page, March 24, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Sending books for signature; read in a London Times poll that both John Banville and Roddy Doyle listed McCarthy as one of "the greatest living novelists writing in English."
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Carbon, 1 page, July 13, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Thanking for signed books.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, February 6, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Regarding John Sheddan and McCarthy's desire to purchase back letters he'd sent to Sheddan. Corresponding note (TMs, 1 p.) from Woolmer about his dealings with Sheddan.
  - Woolmer to Dennis McCarthy. Photocopy, 2 pages, May 15, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Proving fair market appraisals of three signed McCarthy books.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Carbon, 1 page, August 20, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Had coffee with Marisa and Sylvia Erskine.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, September 8, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Alerting McCarthy to bookmarks quoting him. Inquires about future limited editions.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, November 22, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Heard that Thomas Staley met McCarthy in El Paso; urges McCarthy to consider the HRHRC as home for his papers.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, September 24, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Thanking for inscribed Gardener's Son; just back from Vancouver.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Carbon, 1 page, September 14, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Inquiring about a proof copy of Cities of the Plain.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Carbon, 1 page, May 14, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Asking McCarthy to inscribe Cities of the Plain.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Carbon, 1 page, July 24, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Sending Cities of the Plain for inscription; congratulations on wedding and wife's pregnancy.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, September 9, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Thanking for Cities of the Plain; recommends The Bandana, a new opera with a libretto written by Paul Muldoon.
  - McCarthy to Woolmer. Christmas card, January 6, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Signed, and with a print-out of a digital image of the John Francis McCarthy, 5 months.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, January 29, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Inquires about screenplays "Whales and Men" and "Cities of the Plain."
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Carbon, 1 page, November 21, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Working on a new collection; going to Morocco.
  - McCarthy to Woolmer. Printout of digital image, November 28, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Printout of digital image with holograph annotation "John Francis McCarthy 15 months/Nov '99 All best, Cormac."
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Carbon, 1 page, December 4, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Thanking for photograph
  - McCarthy to Woolmer. Printout of digital image, January 28, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Printout of digital image with holograph annotation "John Francis McCarthy, Age 2."
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Photocopy, 1 page, January 30, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Thanking for photograph; Comments on All the Pretty Horses film.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Printout, signed, 1 page, August 11, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Asking McCarthy to sign No Country for Old Men; meeting with Phillip Murray in New York.
  - McCarthy to Woolmer. ALS, 1 page, December 13, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    "Sorry to be so late answering your nice letter…" Has been in Ireland.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Printout, 1 page, December 22, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Sending book for signature; working on Irish Theatre Collection for Princeton.
  - Woolmer to McCarthy. Printout, 1 page, January 25, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Thanking for inscribing No Country for Old Men; is reading Blood Meridian again.
- Writings by Cormac McCarthy, 1982-1994
  Writings by McCarthy includes photocopies of drafts of Blood Meridian, The Crossing, Cities of the Plain, The Road, The Stonemason, and The Gardener's Son. The works are arranged into following subseries: Novels, Plays, and Screenplays.
  - Blood Meridian, 1982-1983
    - Photocopy of the original typescript reproducing holograph corrections that appeared in the original. 468 pp, annotated at bottom right of epilogue page, "Cuidad de Chihuahua December 1982" and "Oct 83 revision" on top left of same. Holograph inscription on the title page: "For Howard with all best wishes Cormac McCarthy."
      - Pages 1-228 of Ms, plus title page, acknowledgements, and quotes. Also included is a photocopy of a January 22, 1985 TL from Peter Shepherd to McCarthy. Pagination is continuous with additional numbered pages: 24a; 169a, b, and c; and 172a. (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Pages 229-451 of Ms, plus 1 p. epilogue. Pagination is continuous from 229-319 with the exception of 254, 255, and 256 on same page. After p. 319, pagination is as follows: 310, 311x, 312, 313, 314x, 315x, 316x, 317, 318x, 319, 320. Pagination is continuous from 320-451 with the exception of 394 and 395 on same page. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Crossing, circa 1994
    - Photocopy of page proofs, 513 pp. complete, printed on rectos only. Preceded by 3 information pp, the first "Cormac McCarthy June" in green felt pen. The second, title page, "Volume Two of The Border" reproduced holograph. The third, the copyright page with "2nd of 3 book contract untitled" with holograph note re the material published in Esquire and a note indicating to whom copies of this typescript should be sent, January 21, 1994. This is a proof for Knopf salesmen.
      - Pages 1-200 plus 3 information pages (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Pages 201-400 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Pages 401-513 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Photocopy of page proofs ready for book printing with line numbering on left side of each page. Loose sheets, 421 pp., printed on rectos only, March 21, 1994. Printed note: "This pass was done in the 'Rough Page' format as requested. Please be advised that standard paging specifications such as window, number lines of the of the last page of a chapter are purposely ignored…" Holograph inscription, "Sent to me for review by McCarthy's editor Gary Fisketjon, Michael Mewshaw."
      - Pages 1-200 plus publication information proofs (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Pages 201-421 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Photocopy of final typescript, 556 pp., loose sheets printed on rectos only. Prepared for limited distribution to Knopf salesmen, with two pages of "key selling points.", May 1994.
      - "Key selling points" fact sheet from Knopf for sales. Includes marketing plans, book description, author information, and previous book sales history. 2 pages (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Pages 1-200 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Pages 201-400 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Pages 401-556 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Photocopy of final typescript, 556 pages., printed on verso and rectos and bound in cloth. Prepared for limited distribution to Knopf salesmen, with two pages of "key selling points", May 1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Cities of the Plain, 1998
    - Photocopy of page proofs, 291 pages, March 5, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Road, undated
    - Photocopy of typescript, 231 pp., printed on verso and rectos and bound in cloth. [Error: includes title Knopf information sheet for From Oslo to Iraq and the Road Map by Edward W. Said.] (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Stonemason: A Play in Five Acts, circa 1994
    - Photocopy of typescript, 107 pp., including cover sheet and title page plus pages 2a and 85a and b. Agent's stamp is on cover sheet. Holograph inscription on title page "For Howard All the best Cormac." The Ecco Press edition is revised from this typescript. The holograph changes that appear in the typescript are mostly incorporated in the Ecco version and there are considerable other changes both in dialogue and in stage directions. Also includes 1 photocopy p. from Publishers Weekly, March 28, 1994 with note on Ecco Press publication. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Gardener's Son, 1978
    - Photocopy of shooting script, 140 pp. Accompanied by the envelope addressed by the author, December 21, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Writings about Cormac McCarthy, 1974-2006
  Writings about McCarthy comprises reviews and articles about McCarthy from Esquire, The New Yorker, Southern Literary Journal, Texas Monthly, and other publications. The writings are arranged alphabetically by author. Also included are a number off clippings files about McCarthy and a small collection of ephemera such as publishers catalogs, flyers, and press packets.
  - Coles, Robert. "The Stranger," in The New Yorker, pages 87-90, August 2, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Ditsky, John. "Further Into Darkness: The Novels of Cormac McCarthy," in The Hollins Circle, vol. 18, no. 2, pages 1-11, April 1981 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Hall, Michael. "Desperately Seeking Cormac," in Texas Monthly, vol. 26, issue 7, pages 76-79; 110-111, July 1998 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Hodge, Roger D. "Blood and Time: Cormac McCarthy at the Twilight of the West," in Harper's Magazine, vol. 312, no. 1869, pages 65-72, February 2006 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Luce, Dianne C. "Cormac McCarthy: A Bibliography," 17 pages, circa 1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Passaro, Vince. "The Best Unknown Writer in America," in Mirabella, pages 52-54, May 1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Privratsky, Kenneth L. "The New McCarthyism: Collecting Cormac McCarthy" in Firsts, pages 24-28, April 1993 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Sepich, John Emil. "A 'bloody dark pastryman': Cormac McCarthy's Recipe for Gunpowder and Historical Fiction in Blood Meridian." (photocopy), undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Sepich, John Emil. "The Dance of History in Cormac McCarthy's Blood Meridian" in The Southern Literary Journal, vol 24, no. 1, Fall 1991, pp 17-31. (photocopy) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Sepich, John Emil. "'What kind of Indians was them?': Some Historical Sources in Cormac McCarthy's Blood Meridian," in The Southern Quarterly, vol. 30, no. 4, Summer 1992, pp. 93-110. (photocopy) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Staley, Thomas F. All the Pretty Horses by Cormac McCarthy (review) in Harper's and Queen, page 76, April 1993 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Wolff, Geoffrey. "Deadbeats, Live Wires: Hanging out with Cormac McCarthy," in Esquire, pages 78-80, March 27, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Wood, James. "Red Planet: the sanguinary sublime of Cormac McCarthy," in The New Yorker, pages 88-93, July 25, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Woodward, Richard W. "Cormac McCarthy's Venomous Fiction," in The New York Times Magazine, pages 28-31, 36, 40, April 19, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Clipping Files, 1965-2005, undated
    - Clippings from John Sheddan, 1965-1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - 1965-1979 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 1994-2005 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Publishers catalogs, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - McCarthy Ephemera, 1993-2000, undated
    - Flyer for the first conference on Cormac McCarthy, Bellarmine College, Louisville, KY (2 copies), October 15-17, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Press packet for All the Pretty Horses. Includes a 5" x 7" b/w photograph of McCarthy (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Vintage Books Reading Group guide to All the Pretty Horses (3 copies) (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Bookmark with McCarthy quote printed at the Bull and Thistle press, Jamaica, VT. (2 bookmarks) (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - "Proceedings of the First European Conference on Cormac McCarthy", June 1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - 1999-2000 season brochure for the McCarter Theatre, Princeton, NJ with listing for world premiere of The Stonemason (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 6)
- J. Howard Woolmer Bibliography Files, 1986-2006
  J. Howard Woolmer bibliography files consist of Woolmer's files and notes on a possible bibliography on McCarthy. Of note are Woolmer's correspondence files regarding collecting McCarthy.
  - Woolmer's correspondence re: collecting McCarthy, 1986-2006 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Woolmer's bibliography files [folder titles as assigned by Woolmer]
    - C. McCarthy – general bibliography (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Cormac McCarthy bibliography (first proof) (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Introduction C McC (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - The Gardener's Son (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - The Stonemason (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Child of God (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Outer Dark (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - The Orchard Keeper (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Suttree (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Blood Meridian (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - All the Pretty Horses (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - The Crossing (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - McCarthy discards (Box 5, Folder 8)